iseepassword.com 2017-09-09

# Privacy Policy of iSeePassword

General Statement

At iSeePassword, your security and privacy is the utmost importance to us. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to iSeePassword's commitment to protect your privacy. iSeePassword will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever. As such, iSeePassword is committed to ensuring that its customers are informed as to how their personal information will be used and kept secure. 

Collection and use of personal information

iSeePassword does not collect any personal data about you on this website or in connection with any other service, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by e-mailing us, by purchasing a product from us, by downloading a product from us, or by registering your product with us, or by using our online feedback form). Information which you provide is used by iSeePassword only in line with the purpose for which you provided it and will not be made available to any third parties, other than information provided to us during the purchase process which may be provided to our online billing provider and our banking institution to enable the purchase to be processed. If iSeePassword has your email address, we may contact you by email to advise you of product updates. You can opt out from receiving these emails at any time. iSeePassword may also contact you in relation to customer support queries which you lodge.

**Support:**

You may need to provide us with personal information when you telephone or email us to request technical assistance in respect of our products, or to request information that you would like to receive relating to our products. 

**Registration:**

Upon registration of one iSeePassword product you will be asked to provide certain information which we will use to record you as an owner of the iSeePassword product and to assist us in providing you with service and information. 

**Purchases:**

If you wish to purchase iSeePassword products from our Store, we will require sufficient information to complete your purchase including your credit card details and your contact details.

Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.
